Harold Corsini Photographs, 1940s-1970s AIS.2007.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Harold Corsini Photographs
1940s-1970s
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Corsini, Harold
AIS.2007.05
55000 items (10 boxes, approximately 55,000 images)
Harold Corsini worked as a freelance photographer in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania and as the official photographer of US Steel. This collection consists of commercial photographs taken for local and national businesses, industrial photographs taken for US Steel, as well as images from WWII and of Southeast Asia and East Africa. Digital reproductions of selected images are available online.
Biography
Born on August 28, 1919 in New York City, New York, Harold Raymond Corsini began a life of photography at the age of sixteen when he took an aerial shot of football players, which is now archived at the George Eastman House. His professional career began in the early 1940s, when he worked briefly for Life magazine. Corsini later joined photographer Roy Stryker on the Standard Oil project. Through this project, Corsini documented the oil company's operations worldwide, including in the Pacific and Saudi Arabia during World War II.
In 1950, Corsini and his wife, Mary, moved to Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, to assist Stryker as head of the photographic department at the Pittsburgh Photographic Library (PPL). While working for the PPL, Corsini, along with other notable photographers such as Clyde Hare, Elliot Erwitt, and Esther Bubley, created a visual record of the city's first Renaissance which began in the 1940s under Mayor David L. Lawrence.
After the PPL disbanded in 1960, Corsini began his own commercial photography business, producing ads for local companies as well as working with larger advertising firms. He later became the official photographer for US Steel. During this period, he chronicled many aspects of the steel industry, including industrial and technical pieces.
After Corsini retired from commercial photography in 1975, he spent nine years teaching photography and design at Carnegie Mellon University. Harold Corsini died on January 1, 2008. Museums around the world have displayed Corsini's photographs. His archived work with the Pittsburgh Photographic Library can be found at the Pennsylvania Department of the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of the collection are available electronically at http://historicpittsburgh.org/collection/harold-corsini-photographs.
Scope and Content Notes
The Harold Corsini Photographs contains photographs produced from the 1940s to the 1970s. Approximately 440 projects are represented in print, negative, and slide form. Many jobs for the US Steel Corporation are industrial in content. Other photographs produced for local and national advertising agencies were captured from locations around the country as well as in the studio. All are commercial and creative in content.
Photographs produced for US Steel artistically represent the essence of the steel industry. From labor to output, and followed by unique advertisements of commercial goods, the culture of the company is widely portrayed. Included are interior and exterior views of steel mills nationwide, depicting machinery, architecture and surrounding landscapes. Employees are creatively portrayed in varying aspects from executive portraits to visual documentaries of steel production.
Corsini worked principally with two main advertising agencies: Kellogg Media Group (KMG) and Batten, Barton, Durstine & Osborn, Inc. (BBD&O). Photographs were also produced for national and local firms including Iron Age Shoes and Westinghouse. Other notable western Pennsylvania companies that Corsini worked with were Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company (PPG), Alcoa, and H. J. Heinz Company. Photographic advertisements vary from studio-based commercial shots featuring products such as food goods, office equipment, and bath fixtures, to on-site views of architecture and interior design.
A small portion of the collection contains personal artistic photographs taken while traveling in India, Thailand, and Egypt highlighting local temples, monuments, and people. Also included are black and white images taken in the Pacific while serving as a WWII correspondent featuring war aircraft and personnel, as well as unrelated commercial portraits and other works.
Arrangement
Collection is arranged numerically by job numbers assigned by the photographer.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions to the collection; however, all copyrights are maintained by the Corsini family. Permission to publish is issued by the Corsini family.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Harold Corsini in July 2007.
Previous Citation
Harold Corsini Photographs, ca. 1943-1970s, AIS.2007.05, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
An index to the photographic jobs was provided by Mr. Corsini at the time of donation. This index can be found in the collection's case file and includes a brief description of work projects numbers 1-2382. While it provides a look into the types of work completed by Mr. Corsini, not all jobs listed are contained within the physical collection held by the archives.
Corsini's work can be in seen repositories nationwide, including The University of Louisville Photographic Archives. Standard Oil (New Jersey) Collection, http://digital.library.louisville.edu/cdm/landingpage/collection/sonj The George Eastman House of Photo Collections which houses two of Corsini's photographs, "Playing football" and "Shoe Repair Shop, Cushing, Oklahoma."
The Library of Congress houses some of Corsini's prints as part of two larger collections, lot 3562 titled, "Standard oil co. (N.J.), New York, N.Y." and lot 11772 titled "Standard Oil Company operations in Northwest Territory, Canada, Feb.-Nov. 1944," and two smaller collections, lot 11778 "Oil fields and oil workers in the vicinity of the Persian Gulf" and lot 11768 "Photographs of workers building a derrick for Carter McAllister well #1 in Oklahoma."
The National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) also contains collections including Corsini's work taken while working for the Petroleum Administration for War, including one collection of 252 photographs entitled, "A Photographic Story of Oil at War: Catalog of Photos for the Press Illustrating the War in the Pacific."
Yale University, Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library houses several images related to image number 02.1645.100. These are found in the Saarinen Collection in Oversize, Box 678, Folder 117 and slides found in Series IV, Box 400, Folder 1090.
The University of Pittsburgh's University Library System has cataloged two volumes, Carnegie Mellon: A Portrait and Floral Art for America, which contain his photographs.
Pittsburgh Photographic Library Records, 1949-1959, UA.90.3.2, University Archives, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Bibliography
Daniel Malloy, "Obituary: Harold Corsini / Photographer who chronicled steel industry Aug. 28, 1919 - Jan. 1, 2008," Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, January 5, 2008.
Nicholas Lemann, Album, "The Way They Were," The New Yorker, April 15, 2002, p. 72.
"The Photographers: Harold Raymond Corsini," Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh, source Roy Stryker: U.S.A., 1943-1950 by Steven W. Plattner (1983).
Photographers; Slides (Photographs); Photographs; Egypt; Dayton (Ohio); Chicago (Ill.); Cleveland (Ohio); Charlotte (N.C.); Urban renewal – Pennsylvania -– Pittsburgh – Photographs; World War, 1939-1945 -- Photography; Travel photography; Landscape photography; Portrait photography -- United States; Photography, Industrial -- United States; Advertising, Industrial -- United States; Photographers -- United States; Franklin (Pa.); Gary (Ind.); India; Rainier, Mount (Wash.); New York (N.Y.); Pittsburgh (Pa.); Seven Springs (Pa.); Thailand; Taiwan; Washington (D.C.); Winchester (Va.); Negatives (Photographic); Business and Industry; Architecture; Aluminum Company of America; Andrews, Gary; Armco Inc.; Batten, Barton, Durstine, & Osborn, Inc.; Burson-Marsteller Associates; Butler, John; Corsini, Harold; De Andre, Frank; H.J. Heinz Company; Haines, David; Inch, Robert; Kellogg Media Group; Papercraft (Firm); Pittsburgh Photographic Library; Pittsburgh Plate Glass Company; Platt, Pierce; PPG Industries; Ross, Robert; Smithsonian Institution; Tayler, William; United States Steel Corporation; Varga, Arnold; Westmoreland Museum of American Art; Wylie, Paul; Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company
- Job Number 134- Pittsburgh Plate Glass- How Lead is Made- Studio Shots (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Job Number 322- Varga- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Children Playing Among Hung Clothes (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Job Number 330- Advertising- Boy and Foam Blocks (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Job Number 752- Gene Boyce- United States Steel- Cockroach (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Job Number 786- Gene Boyce- United States Steel- Bath Tub Shots (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Job Number 924- Al Kiefer- FS&R- Alcoa- New Kensington, Pa., April 14, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Job Number 975A- Pierce Platt- Texas (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Job Number 975B- The Texas Company- Vacuum Pipe Steel- Port Arthur, Texas (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Job Number 975C- Pierce Platt- Midland, Texas (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Job Number 1032- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Sherlock Holmes (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Job Number 1067- Dick Aldroft- Harold [Corsini]-Hunter Fisherman Portraits (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Scope and Contents
  Photographs feature photographer Harold Corsini dressed in hunting and fishing gear.
- Job Number 1209A- United States Steel- New Point Bridge (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Job Number 1209B- United States Steel- New Point Bridge (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Job Number 1289- Civic Arena Aerials (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Job Number 1311- Allegheny Ludlum- New York City and Niagara Falls (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Job Number 1382- Gary [Indiana] Steel Mill (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Job Number 1389- Ed Leet- Brackenridge- Industrial (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Job Number 1403- Pierce Platt- Steel Plate (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Job Number 1404- United States Steel- Duquesne (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Job Number 1406- United States Steel- Homestead Plant (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Job Number 1416- United States Steel- Duquesne (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Job Number 1417- Universal Cyclops- Bridgeville, Pa. (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Job Number 1418- Baby Portraits (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Job Number 1427-Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Traffic [Liberty Tubes; Downtown Pittsburgh] (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Job Number 1430- Pittsburgh Plate Glass- Bean (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Job Number 1440A- United States Steel- Gary [Indiana] (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Job Number 1440B- United States Steel- [Gary Indiana?] (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Job Number 1444- United States Steel- Joliet, Ill. (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Job Number 1455-United States Steel- Homestead (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Job Number 1458- Sparrow Point, Md.- Industrial (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Job Number 1467- Paul Wylie- National Tube- New Orleans (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Job Number 1469- Faulker-Universal Cyclops (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Job Number 1472- Alleghney Ludlum- Dunkirk, NY- Industrial (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Job Number 1484- Chicago High Tower (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Job Number 1486- United States Steel- Test Lab- Monroeville, Pa. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Job Number 1490- BBD&O- Steel Foil and Book (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Job Number 1492- United States Steel- California (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Job Number 1497- United States Steel (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Job Number 1498- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Airport- Washington (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Job Number 1499- BBD&O- Car Seat (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Job Number 1502- BBD&O- United States Steel (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Job Number 1505- Industrial (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Job Number 1506- Cleveland, Ohio (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Job Number 1509- BBD& O- Portraits (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Job Number 1514- Cement (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Job Number 1515 -United States Steel Portraits (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Job Number 1519- Horne's Boxes and Little Girl (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Job Number 1521- Red Valve (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Job Number 1524- United States Steel Cement Blocks (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Job Number 1526- Steel Sound Proof Panels (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Job Number 1529- United States Steel- Chicago (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Job Number 1534- BBD&O- United States Steel Lab (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Job Number 1535- United States Steel- Chicago South Works (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Job Number 1536- Car and Ski Shots at Seven Springs [Pa.] (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Job Number 1542- BBD&O- Car Shots for United States Steel (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Job Number 1395- Metal Extrusions (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Job Number 1548- United States Steel- Car Shots (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Job Number 1549- United States Steel- Washington Street Mill (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Job Number 1550- Martha Malaugh- Baby Portraits (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Job Number 1554- United States Steel (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Job Number 1566- Pierce Platt- United States Steel- Cleveland- Pittsburgh Steel Mills (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Job Number 1567- Pierce Platt- Galvanizing Mill (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Job Number 1570- BBD&O- Industrial- Corrugated Metal (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Job Number 1571- Pierce Platt- United States Steel, 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Job Number 1573- United States Steel (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Job Number 1578- United States Steel- Water on Steel (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Job Number 1580- United States Steel- National Tube- Gary, Indiana (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Job Number 1601- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Ski Photos, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Job Number 1605- Industrial- Ashtabula, OH (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Job Number 1612- Strod Portrait- Violin (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Job Number 1613- Pierce Platt- BBD&O- Irvin Works, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Job Number 1618- BBD&O- Baby Portrait- Duquesne Light (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Job Number 1640- Boy Eating Hot Dogs (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Job Number 1643- United States Steel- "10 cent Steel" (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Job Number 1645- United States Steel- Chicago Building (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Job Number 1648- United States Steel- Monroeville (Pa.) Lab, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Job Number 1650A- ERW Pipe Mill (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Job Number 1650B- Industrial (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Job Number 1652- BBD&O- Golf and Football (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Job Number 1702- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Westinghouse Bus, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Job Number 1704- Pierce Platt- BBD&O- Mesta Equipment (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Job Number 1715- Pipe Mill- National Tube, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Job Number 1722- Paul Wylie- Rockwell- Colored Water (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Job Number 1720- ERW Mill (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Job Number 1723- Westinghouse Condenser (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Job Number 1738- United States Steel- Pipe, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Job Number 1742- BBD&O- Scale with Coins (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Job Number 1750- Phillips Oil Co.- Texas, April 19, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Job Number 1752- United States Steel- High Tention Towers (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Job Number 1753- United States Steel Models (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Job Number 1762- United States Steel Amusement Park, 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Job Number 1763- United States Steel Marine Land (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Job Number 1764- United States Steel- Palm Springs (Ca.) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Job Number 1767- Washington Steel, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Job Number 1774- United States Steel- Chicago, Ill. (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Job Number 1776- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Industrial (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Job Number 1778- Sea Shore (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Job Number 1778- Sea Shore (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Job Number 1780- Runners (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Job Number 1780- Runners (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Job Number 1790- William Trondall- Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Job Number 1790- William Trondall- Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Job Number 1790- William Trondall- Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Job Number 1781- Jim Jordan- United States Steel (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Job Number 1781- Jim Jordan- United States Steel (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Job Number 1794- Body Suits (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Job Number 1796- Westinghouse Metals (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Job Number 1809- Bill Taylor- United States Steel (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Job Number 1817- BBD&O- Sculptor- Harry Bertoia
- Job Number 1826- Westinghouse, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Job Number 1829- Train in Snow- United States Steel (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Job Number 1841-Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Letter K (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Job Number 1843- Ted Eckhart- United States Steel- Blawnox- Johnstown (Pa.) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Job Number 1847- Bill Taylor- United States Steel- Chicago, Illinois (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Job Number 1848- Bill Taylor- Youngstown, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Job Number 1850- Bill Taylor- United States Steel- New Haven, Conn. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Job Number 1856- Pierce Platt- West Virginia Power Company 2nd Time (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Job Number 1865- Bob Inch- FS&R- Alcoa- Simulated Wood (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Job Number 1867- Orange Chain with Stock [?] Background (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Job Number 1868- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- File Cabinet with Typewriter Keys (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Job Number 1872- H. Corsini- Flower [Dandelion] (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Job Number 1878A- Ketchum, MacLeod & Grove, Inc. (KM&G)- Glass Block (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Job Number 1878B- Glass (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Job Number 1883- Washington Steel (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Job Number 1983- United States Steel- Wire Works- Cleveland, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Job Number 1885- Westinghouse- Dayton, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Job Number 1886- Kellogg Media Group- Sky Train- South Park (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Job Number 1888- United States Steel- Transit System Model (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Job Number 1891- Pipe Yard- Oil Job- Texas (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Job Number 1892/93- United States Steel- Gulf Coast- Derrick (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Job Number 1901- MLG Company (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Job Number 1907- Bill Taylor- United States Steel- Corten Statue (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Job Number 1933- United States Steel (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Job Number 1934- Mill Shot- Cleveland, Ohio (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Job Number 1939- Westinghouse (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Job Number 1939B- Industrial (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Job Number 1949- Universal Cyclops (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Job Number 1960- Universal Cyclops- Stainless Steel Heat Treat (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Job Number 1962- United States Steel- Well Drilling (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Job Number 1963- Bob Ross- Rumnell (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Job Number 1966- United States Steel (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Job Number 1967- Robert Carter- Wheeling Steel, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Job Number 1974- Oil Well (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Job Number 1975- Westinghouse- Trafford, Pa. (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Job Number 1984- Crucible Steel- Icehouse (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Job Number 1986- Chicago (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2000- Larry Weimer- United States Steel (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Job Number 2001- North Dakota (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Job Number 2014- Ohio House (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Job Number 2020A- Home Shots (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2020B- House (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Job Number 2020C- All Wood House (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2021- Chicago Civic Center (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2025- Ralph Zitterbaugh- Portraits (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2033- Bob Ross- Ceramic Tiles (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2035- Baby Portraits (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2052- Joe Kravis- Lando- Screws (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2055- Marsteller- Space Car (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2060- Hampton, South Carolina (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2072- Chimney- Scranton, Pa. (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2074- John Butler- Lorraine, Ohio (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2074A- Industrial (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2079- United States Steel- Stainless Steel Sink- Water Down the Drain (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2083- Bob Ross Rochester- New York (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2090- Westinghouse- East Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2091- Steven Damianos Sculpture (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2093- United States Steel New York, January 6, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2096- Kellogg Media Group (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2104- United States Steel (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2106- Albany, New York (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2107- Space Shot (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2109- Bert Delano- Universal Cyclops (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2117- Bert Delano- Universal Cyclops (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2118- Tom Ross- Pennsylvania (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2121- United States Steel- Model of New Pittsburgh Building (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2124- Bituminous Coal Research, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2131- KM&G- Turboblades (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2132- United States Steel (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2133- Tampa, Florida (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Job Number 2137- Fish and Wire (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2141- Kellogg Media Group (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Job Number 2145- United States Steel- Clark Plant (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Job Number 2144- United States Steel- Chrysler Plant (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2147- Industrial- Alaska (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2150- Hammond Tube- Cleveland, Ohio (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2152- Industrial- McKeesport, Pa. (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2154- United States Steel- McKeesport and Oakland (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Job Number 2166- KM&G (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Job Number 2175- United States Steel (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Job Number 2176- KM&G (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Job Number 2178- United States Steel- Ocean Rigs- New Orleans (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Job Number 2179- United States Steel- Lorraine, Ohio (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Job Number 2189- Kellogg Media Group (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Job Number 2191- Tom Ross- Westinghouse- Printed Circuit (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Job Number 2193- United States Steel- Helium Centennial Time Columns Model (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Job Number 2194- Industrial Building Model (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Job Number 2195- Bob Ross, Snails (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Job Number 2197- United States Steel- Swimming Pools- Atlanta, Georgia (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Job Number 2198- Turbine Blades- Studio Shot (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Job Number 2199- J&L Steel (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Job Number 2205A- United States Steel (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Job Number 2205B- 84in. Mill- Gary, Indiana (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Job Number 2209- Westinghouse Music Console (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Job Number 2214- Fox Chapel Steel House (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Job Number 2215A- McCall- Westinghouse (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Job Number 2215B- Industrial (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Job Number 2233- United States Steel- Steel Plates (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Job Number 2234- Industrial (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Job Number 2235- Kellogg Media Group- Westinghouse- Aerospace- Lima, Ohio (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Job Number 2237- General Motors Building- New York, NY (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Job Number 2238A- KM&G- Florida (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Job Number 2238B- KM&G- Florida (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Job Number 2239- United States Steel Cable (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Job Number 2240- United States Steel Pipeline- Mississippi (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Job Number 2241- Papercraft (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Job Number 2245- Exploding Cabinet (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Job Number 2254- Harrisburg, Pa. (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Job Number 2261- Architecturals (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Job Number 2263- Turbine Plant (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Job Number 2264- Hand with Sponge (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Job Number 2265- Kids Portraits (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Job Number 2267- Industrial and Portraits (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Job Number 2268- Motor- East Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Job Number 2269- Fecker Optical (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Job Number 2270- Girl Portrait (Box 5, Folder 40)